Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Correspondence, 1969 - 1992; F-225-2; 51 cm of textual records
  - Departmental correspondence, 1971 - 1991; F-225-2-4; 34 cm of textual records
    - Linguistics, 1990 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-33 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
- Graduate program proposals, 1976 - 1994; F-225-3; 41 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to new graduate program proposals (Master or Ph.D. level) submitted to the Dean of Graduate Studies for review and includes program descriptions, course outlines, library reviews, letters of support from external academics, faculty C.V.'s, and draft versions of final proposals sent to Senate. Records include correspondence and working papers, reports, and statistics.
  - Introduction of new programs, 1976 - 1982; F-225-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-38.
  - M.Sc. in Geography, 1978 - 1979; F-225-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-44.
  - Master's in Publishing, vol. 1, 1986 - 1990; F-225-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
  - Master's in Publishing, vol. 2, 1986 - 1990; F-225-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
  - Master's in Publishing, vol. 3, 1986 - 1990; F-225-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-11)
  - Master's in Publishing, vol. 4, 1986 - 1990; F-225-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-11)
  - Master's in Publishing, vol. 5, 1986 - 1990; F-225-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-11)
  - Master of Arts, Liberal Studies, vol. 1, 1986 - 1992; F-225-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-11)
  - Master of Arts, Liberal Studies, vol. 2, 1986 - 1992; F-225-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-11)
  - Master of Arts, Liberal Studies, vol. 3, 1986 - 1992; F-225-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 225-11)
  - Master of Arts, Liberal Studies, vol. 4, 1986 - 1992; F-225-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 225-11)
  - Master of Aquaculture, 1987 - 1988; F-225-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 225-12)
  - Master of Fine Arts, vol. 1, 1987 - 1991; F-225-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 225-12)
  - Master of Fine Arts, vol. 2, 1987 - 1991; F-225-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 225-12)
  - Master of Fine Arts, vol. 3, 1987 - 1991; F-225-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 225-12)
  - Master of Fine Arts, vol. 4, 1987 - 1991; F-225-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 225-12)
  - Master of Fine Arts, vol. 5, 1987 - 1991; F-225-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 225-12)
  - Master of Arts in Spanish, 1987 - 1993; F-225-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 225-12)
  - Ph.D. in Engineering Science, vol. 1, 1988 - 1989; F-225-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 225-12)
  - Ph.D. in Engineering Science, vol. 2, 1988 - 1989; F-225-3-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 225-12)
  - Ph.D. in Engineering Science, vol. 3, 1988 - 1989; F-225-3-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 225-13)
  - Master of Arts, Latin American Studies, vol. 1, 1989 - 1992; F-225-3-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 225-13)
  - Master of Arts, Latin American Studies, vol. 2, 1989 - 1992; F-225-3-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 225-13)
  - Master of Arts, Latin American Studies, vol. 3, 1989 - 1992; F-225-3-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 225-13)
  - Master of Arts, Latin American Studies, vol. 4, 1989 - 1992; F-225-3-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 225-13)
  - Joint MRM/MBA degree, vol. 1, 1990 - 1993; F-225-3-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 225-13)
  - Joint MRM/MBA degree, vol. 2, 1990 - 1993; F-225-3-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 225-13)
  - Master of Arts, French, vol. 1, 1991 - 1994; F-225-3-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 225-13)
  - Master of Arts, French, vol. 2, 1991 - 1994; F-225-3-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 225-13)
- Committee records, 1965 - 1995; F-225-4; 1.97 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the Dean's correspondence with, and participation on, various campus and non-campus committees. The Dean served as Chair for many of the Senate Committees and was on the executive board for non-campus committees including the Canadian Association for Graduate Studies and the Western Canadian Deans of Graduate Studies Committee. For the complete list of committees, see the sub-series list below. Records include correspondence and working papers, agendas and minutes, reports, and financial papers.
  Ad Hoc Committee on Graduate – Faculty Relations; Computing Centre Policy Committee; President's Research Grant Committee; Senate Commitee on Academic Discipline; Senate Policy Committee on Scholarships, Awards and Bursaries; Task Force on Graduate Tuition Fees; University of Havana Exchange Steering Committee; University Review Committee; Working Group on Strategic Planning
  - Academic Planning Committee, 1970 - 1975; F-225-4-1; 3 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1970 - 1972; F-225-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-13.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1973 - 1975; F-225-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-14)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Graduate Student-Faculty Relations, 1992 - 1993; F-225-4-2; 3 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1992 - 1993; F-225-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-14)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1992 - 1993; F-225-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-14)
  - Canadian Association for Graduate Studies, 1978 - 1992; F-225-4-3; 12 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1978 - 1983; F-225-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-6-0-0-1.
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1983 - 1984; F-225-4-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-6-0-0-2.
    - Graduate student attendance, 1983 - 1984; F-225-4-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-6-0-0-6.
    - CFH and SSFC survey, 1984; F-225-4-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-6-0-0-7.
    - Correspondence and minutes, vol. 1, 1984; F-225-4-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-6-0-0-3.
    - Correspondence and minutes, vol. 2, 1984; F-225-4-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-6-0-0-4.
    - Correspondence and minutes, vol. 1, 1985; F-225-4-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-6-0-0-5.
    - Correspondence and minutes, vol. 2, 1985; F-225-4-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-15)
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1991 - 1992; F-225-4-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-15)
  - Canadian Association for Graduate Studies Executive Committee, 1992; F-225-4-4; 2 cm of textual records
    - Executive Committee, 1992; F-225-4-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-15)
  - Computing Centre Policy Committee, 1978 - 1980; F-225-4-5; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1978 - 1980; F-225-4-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-25.
  - Eastern Indonesia University Development Project Advisory Committee, 1986 - 1992; F-225-4-6; 15 cm of textual records
    - Reports, 1986 - 1987; F-225-4-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-15)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1988; F-225-4-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-15)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1988; F-225-4-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-15)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 3, 1988; F-225-4-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-16)
    - Travel to Indonesia, 1988 - 1989; F-225-4-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-16)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1990; F-225-4-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-16)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1990; F-225-4-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-16)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1991; F-225-4-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-16)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1992; F-225-4-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-16)
  - President's Research Grant Committee, 1965 - 1981; F-225-4-7; 10 cm of textual records
    - Faculty awards - correspondence and reports, 1965 - 1978; F-225-4-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-8-1-0-6.
    - Terms of reference, 1968 - 1977; F-225-4-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-8-1-0-1.
    - Budget, 1970 - 1980; F-225-4-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-8-1-0-7.
    - Statement of funding and awards, 1971 - 1976; F-225-4-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-8-1-0-8.
    - Research assistants pay rates, 1972 - 1973; F-225-4-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-8-1-0-9.
    - Meeting minutes, 1972 - 1977; F-225-4-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-8-1-0-3.
    - Agendas, 1972 - 1980; F-225-4-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-8-1-0-2.
    - Annual reports, 1973 - 1977; F-225-4-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-8-1-0-10.
    - Meeting minutes, 1977 - 1980; F-225-4-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-8-1-0-4.
    - Correspondence, 1978 - 1981; F-225-4-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-8-1-0-11.
  - Search Committee, 1976 - 1981; F-225-4-8; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1976 - 1981; F-225-4-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-22.
  - Senate Committee on Academic Discipline, 1980 - 1981; F-225-4-9; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1980 - 1981; F-225-4-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-1.
  - Senate Committee on Awards and Bursaries, 1975 - 1985; F-225-4-10; 8 cm of textual records
    - Meeting minutes, 1975 - 1980; F-225-4-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-4.
    - Meeting minutes, 1982 - 1983; F-225-4-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-17)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-5.
    - Correspondence with SCAB Secretary, 1982 - 1985; F-225-4-10-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-8.
    - Meeting minutes, vol. 1, 1984; F-225-4-10-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-7.
    - Meeting minutes, vol. 2, 1984; F-225-4-10-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-6.
    - Meeting minutes, vol. 1, 1985; F-225-4-10-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-9.
    - Meeting minutes, vol. 2, 1985; F-225-4-10-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-10.
  - Senate Graduate Awards Adjudication Committee, 1989 - 1991; F-225-4-11; 4 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1989; F-225-4-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-18)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1990; F-225-4-11-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-18)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1991; F-225-4-11-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-18)
  - Senate Graduate Studies Committee, 1979 - 1991; F-225-4-12; 19 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1979 - 1984; F-225-4-12-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-18)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-13.
    - Correspondence and reports, 1989; F-225-4-12-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-18)
    - Agenda and minutes, vol. 1, 1989; F-225-4-12-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-19)
    - Agenda and minutes, vol. 2, 1989; F-225-4-12-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-19)
    - Agenda and minutes, vol. 3, 1989; F-225-4-12-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-19)
    - Agenda and minutes, vol. 4, 1989; F-225-4-12-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-19)
    - Agenda and minutes, vol. 1, 1990; F-225-4-12-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-19)
    - Agenda and minutes, vol. 2, 1990; F-225-4-12-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-19)
    - Agenda and minutes, vol. 1, 1991; F-225-4-12-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-19)
    - Agenda and minutes, vol. 2, 1991; F-225-4-12-0-10 (Archival box - standard 225-20)
    - Agenda and minutes, vol. 3, 1991; F-225-4-12-0-11 (Archival box - standard 225-20)
  - Senate Graduate Studies Committee Assessment Committee for New Graduate Programs, 1974 - 1995; F-225-4-13; 71 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1974 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-20)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-18.
    - Ph.D. in Education, vol. 1, 1979 - 1982; F-225-4-13-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-20)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-36.
    - Ph.D. in Education, vol. 2, 1979 - 1982; F-225-4-13-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-20)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-37.
    - Ph.D. in Communications, vol. 1, 1981 - 1983; F-225-4-13-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-20)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-24.
    - Ph.D. in Communications, vol. 2, 1981 - 1983; F-225-4-13-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-20)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-25.
    - Women Studies proposal, vol. 1, 1981 - 1984; F-225-4-13-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-21)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-31.
    - Women Studies proposal, vol. 2, 1981 - 1984; F-225-4-13-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-21)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-32.
    - Women Studies proposal, vol. 3, 1981 - 1984; F-225-4-13-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-21)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-33.
    - Women Studies proposal, vol. 4, 1981 - 1984; F-225-4-13-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-21)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-34.
    - Women Studies proposal, vol. 5, 1981 - 1984; F-225-4-13-0-10 (Archival box - standard 225-21)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-35.
    - M.B.A. (daytime), vol. 1, 1981 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-11 (Archival box - standard 225-21)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-26.
    - M.B.A. (daytime), vol. 2, 1981 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-12 (Archival box - standard 225-21)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-27.
    - M.B.A. (daytime), vol. 3, 1981 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-13 (Archival box - standard 225-22)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-30.
    - M.B.A. (daytime), vol. 4, 1981 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-14 (Archival box - standard 225-22)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-29.
    - Ph.D. in Criminology, vol. 1, 1981 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-15 (Archival box - standard 225-22)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-38.
    - Ph.D. in Criminology, vol. 2, 1981 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-16 (Archival box - standard 225-22)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-39.
    - Ph.D. in Criminology, vol. 3, 1981 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-17 (Archival box - standard 225-22)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-40.
    - Ph.D. in Criminology, vol. 4, 1981 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-18 (Archival box - standard 225-22)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-41.
    - Ph.D. in Criminology, vol. 5, 1981 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-19 (Archival box - standard 225-22)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-42.
    - Ph.D. in Computing Science, 1982; F-225-4-13-0-20 (Archival box - standard 225-23)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-43.
    - M.B.A. (Executive), 1982 - 1984; F-225-4-13-0-21 (Archival box - standard 225-23)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-48.
    - M.Sc. in Statistics, vol. 1, 1982 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-22 (Archival box - standard 225-23)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-21. Creator's original file classification code: 3.1.70.
    - M.Sc. in Statistics, vol. 2, 1982 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-23 (Archival box - standard 225-23)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-22. Creator's original file classification code: 6.1.5.7.00.
    - Master's of Applied Science in Engineering Science, 1983 - 1985; F-225-4-13-0-24 (Archival box - standard 225-23)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-23. Creator's original file classification code: 7.15.
    - New program ideas, 1984; F-225-4-13-0-25 (Archival box - standard 225-23)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-20.
    - Ph.D. in Philosophy (SFU/UBC), vol. 1, 1986 - 1994; F-225-4-13-0-26 (Archival box - standard 225-23)
    - Ph.D. in Philosophy (SFU/UBC), vol. 2, 1986 - 1994; F-225-4-13-0-27 (Archival box - standard 225-24)
    - Master's in Aquaculture, vol. 1, 1987 - 1991; F-225-4-13-0-28 (Archival box - standard 225-24)
    - Master's in Aquaculture, vol. 2, 1987 - 1991; F-225-4-13-0-29 (Archival box - standard 225-24)
    - Ph.D. in Engineering Science, 1989 - 1991; F-225-4-13-0-30 (Archival box - standard 225-24)
    - Master's in Publishing, vol. 1, 1989 - 1994; F-225-4-13-0-31 (Archival box - standard 225-24)
    - Master's in Publishing, vol. 2, 1989 - 1994; F-225-4-13-0-32 (Archival box - standard 225-24)
    - M.A. in Gerontology, vol. 1, 1991 - 1995; F-225-4-13-0-33 (Archival box - standard 225-25)
    - M.A. in Gerontology, vol. 2, 1991 - 1995; F-225-4-13-0-34 (Archival box - standard 225-25)
    - M.A./Ph.D. in Linguistics, 1992 - 1994; F-225-4-13-0-35 (Archival box - standard 225-25)
    - Ph.D. in Resource and Environmental Management, vol. 1, 1993 - 1994; F-225-4-13-0-36 (Archival box - standard 225-25)
    - Ph.D. in Resource and Environmental Management, vol. 2, 1993 - 1994; F-225-4-13-0-37 (Archival box - standard 225-25)
    - Ph.D. in Resource and Environmental Management, vol. 3, 1993 - 1994; F-225-4-13-0-38 (Archival box - standard 225-25)
  - Senate Graduate Studies Committee Executive Committee, 1970 - 1986; F-225-4-14; 6 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1970 - 1975; F-225-4-14-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-26)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-10.
    - Terms of reference, 1971 - 1976; F-225-4-14-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-26)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-11.
    - Correspondence, 1980 - 1982; F-225-4-14-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-26)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-11.
    - Correspondence, 1983 - 1986; F-225-4-14-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-26)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-12.
  - Senate Policy Committee on Scholarships, Awards and Bursaries, 1989 - 1992; F-225-4-15; 5 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1989; F-225-4-15-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-26)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1991; F-225-4-15-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-26)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1992; F-225-4-15-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-26)
  - Task Force on Graduate Tuition Fees, 1993; F-225-4-16; 3 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1993; F-225-4-16-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-26)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1993; F-225-4-16-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-27)
  - University of Havana Exchange Steering Committee, 1991 - 1992; F-225-4-17; 3 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes, reports and contracts, 1991; F-225-4-17-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-27)
    - Correspondence, minutes, reports and contracts, 1992; F-225-4-17-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-27)
  - University Research Ethics Review Committee, 1972 - 1981; F-225-4-18; 6 cm of textual records
    - Miscellaneous guidelines, 1972 - 1977; F-225-4-18-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-27)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-4-0-0-1.
    - Correspondence, 1975 - 1980; F-225-4-18-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-27)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-4-0-0-3.
    - Meeting agendas and minutes, 1978 - 1979; F-225-4-18-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-27)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-4-0-0-4.
    - SFU guidelines, 1980 - 1981; F-225-4-18-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-27)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-4-0-0-2.
  - University Review Committee, 1976 - 1978; F-225-4-19; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1976 - 1978; F-225-4-19-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-27)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-26.
  - Western Canadian Deans of Graduate Studies Committee, 1979 - 1992; F-225-4-20; 17 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1979 - 1984; F-225-4-20-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-6-0-0-8.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1979 - 1984; F-225-4-20-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-6-0-0-9.
    - Graduate student short courses, 1980 - 1985; F-225-4-20-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-6-0-0-10.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1990; F-225-4-20-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-28)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1990; F-225-4-20-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-28)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1991; F-225-4-20-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-28)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1991; F-225-4-20-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-29)
    - Recruitment Fair, 1992; F-225-4-20-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-29)
    - Meeting agendas and minutes, 1992; F-225-4-20-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-29)
  - Working Group on Strategic Planning, 1990 - 1991; F-225-4-21; 5 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1990 - 1991; F-225-4-21-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-29)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1990 - 1991; F-225-4-21-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-29)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 3, 1990 - 1991; F-225-4-21-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-29)
- Financial records, 1985 - 1992; F-225-5; 7 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the financial administration of the Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies. The budget records include correspondence, working papers, reports, and statistics.
  - Budget, 1985 - 1986; F-225-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-29)
  - Budget, 1986 - 1987; F-225-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-29)
  - Budget, 1987 - 1988; F-225-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-30)
  - Budget, 1988 - 1989; F-225-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-30)